股票与债券水涨船高...
Stocks and bonds are moving higher...
摩妮卡 我们为什么在看财经频道?
Hey Monical, why are we watching the Business Channel?
因为那天我无意中看到
'Cause I was going by it the other day
有支股票跟我的名字缩写一样 MEG
and I saw there was a stock with my initials, MEG on it.
有时要等23个小时才能看到它再出现
Sometimes it takes two or three hours before it comes up again.
但当它出来的时候 相当爽
But when it does, it's pretty exciting.
额 亲爱的 你真的得找份工作了
Hmm, okay, honey, you really need a job.
摩妮卡 说到这 老爸说他认识个人
Mon, speaking of which, Dad says he knows someone
你要是想面试可以打电话给他      真的么?
you can call for an interview.        Really?
就是这个! 这是今天第三个征兆了 就是这个
Okay, right there! That's the third sign today. Right there.
我替在座的各位问一句...什么?
On behalf of everyone, I'd just like to say, "Huh?"
不是 是因为你刚才说"老爸"
No, cause you just said "dad".
而且今天不论我去哪里
And everywhere I go today...
我不停得到让我去见我爸爸的征兆
I keep getting signs telling me to go see my father.
就好像当我过来这里时
Like when I was walking over here,
经过一家自助餐厅"布菲"
and I passed a buffet.
"布菲" 那是我爸爸的姓
Which is my father's last name.
他们当时正在上法兰克福香肠
And they were serving franks
结尾去掉"福"后 法兰克就是他的名字
which is his first name, minus the "s" at the end.
没错
Yes.
而且那里的烤肉架上 有只烤鸡在上面转
And there was a rotisserie with a spinning chicken.
他的印度名字?
His Indian name?
不 因为我上次"胆小如鸡"
No. Because I chickened out the last time
没有去见他 这都是巧合吗? 我可不这么认为
when I tried to meet him. So coincidences? I don't think so.
很古怪      诡异
Very freaky.        Eerie.
好吧 谁想要最后一个汉堡?
Okay, so uh, who wants the last hamburger?
哦 好吧 够了 现在我必须要去见他了
Oh, alright, that's it. Now I have to go see him
为什么?
Why?
汉堡? 麦当劳?
Hamburger? McDonald's?
老麦当劳有个农场 我爸爸是个药剂师
Old McDonald had a farm. My dad is a pharmacist.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第21集
两个小流氓 The One With the Two Bullies
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：悠悠慕雪
啊 累死我了
Man, I am so beat.
对啊
Oh, yeah.
干脆不要去打壁球了 我们就待在这儿怎么样?
Hey, you just wanna forget racquetball and hang out here?
好啊
Yeah, all right.
嗨 你们坐了我们的位子
Hey, you're in our seats.
哦 不好意思 我们不知道
Oh, sorry, we didn't know.
嗨 我们刚才坐在这里的
Hey, we were sitting there.
好吧 还有另外一种说法
Okay. There is one more way to say it.
谁知道?
Who knows it?
你说这话是自以为风趣么?
Is that supposed to be funny?
不 只是想说得生动而已
Actually, I was going for colorful.
这家伙是怎么回事?      你是怎么回事?
What's with this guy?        What's with you?
没什么 他没怎么样
Uh, nothing. Nothing's with him.
慢慢享受你们的咖啡吧
Enjoy your coffee.
刚才怎么回事?
What just happened?
我只是拿了你的帽子
I just took your hat.
你看 我也可以很风趣
See, I can be funny too.
我的笑话就是 我拿了你的帽子
My, my joke is that I took your hat.
那很好笑
That is funny.
我能拿回来吗?
Can I have it back?
不行
No.
不行?      不行
No?        No.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
你们知道吗? 我认为你很风趣
You know what? I think you're very funny.
那个帽子笑话很不错
Kudos on that hat joke.
但是 兄弟 把帽子还给他吧
But come on, guys, just give him back the hat.
为什么?
Why should we?
因为那是一顶很特别的帽子
Because it's a special hat.
他买这顶帽子是因为那天他情绪低落
See, he bought it because he was feeling down one day.
所以他才买了这帽子
So he got the hat
让自己高兴一点 你知道么?
to cheer himself up, you know?
钱德他...      别说了 不要再说了
Now, Chandler...        Stop talking. Stop talking now.
我直说了吧 你真的偷我的帽子?
Let me get this straight. You're actually stealing my hat?
有问题吗?
You got a problem with that?
我只是想确认一下我们达成共识了
I just want to make sure we're on the same page.
面试如何?
How'd the interview go?
糟透了
It bit.
那是个50年代主题餐厅
It was a 50's theme restaurant.
我得穿着戏服做饭 还要在柜台上跳舞
I'd have to cook in a costume and dance on the counter
我以前是艺术家咖啡馆的二厨
I mean, I was a sous-chef at Cafe des Artistes.
我怎么能在这样的快餐店做东西?
How can I take a job where I have to make something called Laverne and Curly Fries?
那就别干了      我怎么能不干?
Don't do it.        How can I not do it?
我只剩下127块存款了
I have $127 in the bank.
摩妮卡 放轻松 去拿瓶啤酒
Monica, relax. Go get a beer.
我不想喝啤酒
I don't want a beer
谁说是要给你的?
Who said it was for you?
大家好      大家好
Hi.        Hi.
你们怎么了?
What's the matter with you?
有两个烂人在咖啡厅拿走了我的帽子
Some mean guys at the coffeehouse took my hat.
不会吧      开玩笑吧
No.        You're kidding.
太荒谬了 他们是流氓
It was ridiculous. These guys, they were bullies.
真正的流氓
Actual bullies.
我们都是成人了 这种事情不应该再发生了
You know, we're grown ups. This kind of stuff isn't supposed to happen anymore.
嗨      嗨
Oh, hi.        Hi.
哦...
Oh..
不对 等等 我身边一个人也没有
Oh, no, wait a minute. I have no one.
我们下去把你的帽子拿回来
Let's go down there and get your hat back.
算了吧 很可能都已经剥开分块卖了
Forget it. It's probably stripped and sold for parts by now.
嗨 我涨了!      什么?
Hey. I went up!        What?
我的股票 MEG 它升了两点
My stock, MEG, it went up two points.
嗨 你们意识到如果昨天我把127块投资到我身上
Do you realize that if I'd invested my $127 in myself yesterday...
现在我就有...额...比现在多得多的钱了
that I'd, like, have a lot more than that today.
你们猜怎么着? 我要做这个
You know what? I'm gonna do it.
做什么?      把钱都投资到我身上
Do what?        Put all my money in me.
摩妮卡 你在说什么? 你对股票市场一无所知
Monica, what are you talking about? You don't know a thing about the stock market.
有什么要知道的? 买啊卖啊 高啊低啊 熊市 牛市
What's to know? Buy, sell. High, low. Bears, bulls.
嗨 曼哈顿
Yes Manhattan.
对 我要电话号码 股票
Telephone number to the stock...
交易所的
selling store.
看吧 我就跟你说带枕头来是个好主意
See? Didn't I tell you these pillows would be a good idea?
哦 天呐
Oh, God.
我们到了
Here we go.
有生以来第一次 我要说 "你好 生父!"
For the first time in my life, I'm gonna say "Hi birth father!"
我们爱你 我们支持你      祝你好运
We love you. We're here for you.        Good luck.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗨 瑞秋 额 想吃点三明治吗?
Hey, Rach, you, uh, want some sandwich?
那里面都夹了些什么?
Oh, what is in that?
橄榄面包和火腿酱 没有蛋黄酱
Olive loaf and ham spread. No mayo.
当然不 因为蛋黄酱 会把这个弄得很恶心
No, because mayo, that would make it gross.
嘿 嘿 不 哦哦...
Hey, hey. No. oh. oh. oh.
跑 菲比 快跑!      小狗狗 别这样!
Run, Phoebe, run.        No, no, doggy, please!
我热爱所有的动物 别这样! 放开我!
I do so want to love all animals. Please, no. Back off!
去拿骨头? 你有骨头吗?      开什么玩笑?
Get him a bone, get a bone. You gotta bone?        Are you kidding me?
别咬了!
Look, kibbles! Bits, oh!
老天 好吧! 从我腿上滚开 你这个混帐东西!
Get the hell off my leg, you yippity piece of crap!
好吧 我们有麻烦了
Okay. All right. We have a problem.
你为什么不把他的蹦床拿走?
Well why don't you just reach out and take his trampoline?
这样吧 我知道怎么做了
Okay, here, I know what we can do.
嗨 嗨 嗨 不!
Hey. Hey. Hey, no!
狗狗 去吃那块三明治!
Okay, doggy, get the sandwich! Aah!
去吃三明治 乖狗狗 吃三明治!
Go get the sandwich! Good doggy. Get the sandwich!
乔伊 那狗肯舔自己却不碰你的三明治
Okay, Joey. The dog will lick himself but he will not touch your sandwich.
这说明什么?
What does that tell you?
他要是不吃的话 我还想吃呢      你疯了吗?
If he's not gonna eat it, I will.        Are you crazy?
菲比 那只是一只小狗
Pheebs, he's just a little dog. Aah!
嗨      怎么了?
Hey.        What?
你是不是要成为一个21世纪不动产经纪人
Do you have to be a Century 21 real estate agent
才能穿那些很酷的外套?
to get to wear those really cool jackets?
你就跟姑娘们说这个?
Do you say this stuff to girls?
嗨 那不是以前戴你帽子的家伙吗?
Hey, isn't that the guy who used to wear your hat?
看他们现在坐在哪儿
And look where they're sitting.
你开玩笑吧? 你们才刚刚进门
You're joking, right? You guys just walked through the door.
也许我们没跟他们说清楚      对
Maybe we didn't make it clear enough.        Yeah.
这沙发属于我们
This couch belongs to us.
好吧 这么办吧 你们叫这沙发
I'll tell you what, you call the couch
然后我们也叫它沙发
and then we'll call the couch
然后看它会走向谁
and we'll see who it comes to.
你们知道我在想什么吗? 你们怎么还坐在这里?
You know what I keep wondering? Why you two are still sitting here.
够了
All right, that's it.
我受够了
I have had enough of this, all right?
阿甘
Gunther.
这两个家伙想抢我们的座位
These guys are trying to take our seat.
兄弟 他们先来的
Fellas, these guys were here first.
不好意思 没注意到
Oh, sorry, didn't realize.
行了
There you go.
谢谢你 阿甘
Thank you, Gunther
我们不是一定要这样才行的
We didn't want to have to go and do that.
他告我们的状?
He told on us?
你告我们的状?
You told on us?
额 兄弟 你们没给我别的选择
Well, pal, you didn't give me much of a choice.
别玩他的东西      我知道
Don't play with his thing.        I know.
好吧
All right.
我们到外面谈谈吧
Let's take this outside.
"我们到外面谈谈"?
"Let's, let's take this outside"?
谁这么说话啊?
Who talks like that?
马上就要痛宰你的人这么说话
The guy who's about to kick your ass talks like that.
你一定要问是吧?      是的
You had to ask.        Yeah.
好吧 知道么
Okay, okay, look. See
我们并不打算跟你们打架
the thing is, we're, we're not gonna fight you guys.
那有个条件
Then here's the deal.
只要你们永远不在这里出现 就不用跟我们打架
You won't have to, so long as you never ever show your faces in this coffee house ever again.
我认为你用阿甘用得太早了
I think you played the Gunther card too soon.
嗨 菲比 我想你现在能去了
Hey, Phoebs, I think you're good to go.
好的 我不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
我只是觉得这是一个很糟的征兆
I just think that this was a really bad sign.
你知道 就像一开始就是野兽
You know, I mean, like the beast at the threshold, you know.
只是除了祖母以外 我没有别的亲人了
It's just I have no family left, you know, except for my grandmother
但是面对现实 她不可能一直都在
But let's face it. She's not gonna be around forever.
不管她怎么说
Despite what she says.
我还有个妹妹
And I have a sister
从我们待过同一子宫后 我几乎不怎么和她说话
who I've barely spoken to since we shared a womb.
我不知道 这是我真正的父亲
I don't know. This is my real father...
我只希望事情顺利
and I want things to be, like, just right.
菲比 我完全理解
Yeah Phoebes I completely understand.
你想怎么做都好
Yeah, whatever you need.
你想回家吗?
Hey, you want to go home?
好吧 多谢了 再一次 对不起
Okay, thanks. Sorry again.
那是什么?
What was that?
我想一开始的路障已经清掉了
Uh, I'm guessing the threshold's clear now.
我要买5股SGJ 现在就要
I want to buy five shares of SGJ and I wanna buy them now.
快点 时间就是金钱 朋友!
Come on, time is money, my friend!
多谢! 哇哦
Thank you! Whoo!
"时间就是金钱 朋友"?
"Time is money, my friend"?
是呀 你错过了"钱能生钱"
You missed "Takes money to make money"
还有"别逼我过去痛宰你们这些华尔街浑蛋"
and "Don't make me come down there and kick your Wall Street butt"
我在早餐之前赚了17块 你呢?
Hey, I made $17 before breakfast. What have you done?
我在这里吃的早餐 所以从技术角度看 我省了3块5
Well, I had breakfast here, so technically I saved $3.50.
你怎么赚到17块的?
How did you make $17?
嗯 我的金融常识有待加强的朋友
Well, my financially challenged friends...
我用我的钱分别买了些CHP和ZXY
I split my money and I bought some shares of CHP and ZXY.
为什么要买这些?
How come those?
嗯 CHP是因为我以前很喜欢Erik Estrada这个演员
Well CHP because I used to have a crush on Erik Estrada.
ZXY是因为我觉得它听起来像"zexy"(性感)
And ZXY because I think it sounds "zexy"
那MEG呢?
Ahem, what happened to MEG?
MEG不错 但是我甩了她
MEG was good for me, but I dumped her.
你知道 我的座右铭是"下跌之前滚开"
My motto is "Get out before they go down."
这绝对不是我的座右铭
That is so not my motto.
嗨      嗨 菲比
Hey.        Hey, Phoebes.
那狗怎么样了?
Oh. hey, how's the dog?
我跟兽医谈过了 北边的人真是很友善
Okay. I talked to the vet. People are so nice upstate.
他说小家伙会没事的 我明天就可以去接他
Oh, anyway he said the little fellas gonna be okay, and I can get him tomorrow.
很好      多谢老天
Good.        Oh, thank God.
不过他不得不多缝几针
But he did have to have, like, a bunch of stitches.
而且他说除非太阳从西边出来
And he said that only once in a blue moon
狗的耳朵才可能重新长出来
does a dogs ear grow back.
所以我还在期望中
So still hoping.
菲比 现在你会打电话给你父亲
Ok, so Phoebes, now are you gonna call your dad
让他知道他的狗没事了吧?
to let him know that his dog is okay?
我不想跟我爸在电话上相认
I don't want to meet my father over the phone.
我要说什么? "我是菲比 你抛弃的女儿
What will I say, like "Hi, I'm the daughter you abandoned.
哦 顺便说一句 我弄伤了你的狗"
Oh, by the way, I broke your dog."
菲比 如果你愿意 我来帮你打
Hey, Phoebes, if you want, I'll do it.
好的
Okay.
听着 别说任何关于我的事情
Listen, just don't say anything about me, okay?
别...
Don't...
用太久电话
be too long with the phone.
股票市场关了后她会是个更好的朋友
She'll be a much better friend once the market closes.
是个女人
It's a woman.
跟她说话
So talk to her.
你好 布非太太
Uh, hello, Mrs. Buffay.
我知道你的狗在哪里
I know where your dog is.
我想让你知道 它会在24小时内回到你身边
I want you to know he'll be returned to you almost as good as new
完好无损 跟全新的一样
within 24 hours.
再见
Uh, goodbye.
为什么是那种声音?      很难说
Why the voice?        Hard to say.
先生 您的卡布其诺
Your cappuccino, sir
谢谢
Thank you.
我觉得这里比咖啡店好多了      绝对的
You know, I think this is much better than the coffee house.        Absolutely.
这怎么不会溶在水里?
How come it's not mixing with the water?
包装上说你要不停的搅动
The package says you have to keep it moving.
边搅边喝  边搅边喝 千万别停下来
Stir and drink, stir and drink, never let it settle.
这太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
这样吧 等我从我侄女的洗礼回来后
I tell you what, after I get back from my nieces christening
我跟你们一起到咖啡厅
I'll go down to the coffee house with you
我们一起享受一杯好咖啡 好吧
and we'll have a nice cup of coffee alright.
没问题 有乔伊在哈
No problem. Joey's there, hmm?
好      不行
Okay.        No.
不行?      不行
No?        No.
我不想要每次想喝杯好咖啡 都要有乔伊陪着
I don't want to have to have Joey with me every time I want a decent cup of coffee.
我不想我后半生都喝这"K"开头的卡布其诺
And I don't wanna spend the rest of my life drinking cappuccino with a "k"
我说 你和我下去勇敢面对那些家伙
I say you and I go back down there and stand up to those guys.
等等 猛男
All right, hang on a second there, Custer.
罗斯 你以前被痛揍过吗?
Yeah really Ross, have you ever been beaten up before?
当然
Yeah, sure.
被摩妮卡以外的人?      没有
By someone besides Monica?        No.
那又怎样?
So what?
被痛揍又怎样?
So we get beaten up.
也许那是每个男人一生中都要经历的事情
Maybe that's something a man has to go through once in his life.
就像成年礼之类的东西
You know, like a, like a right of passage or something.
我们能不能只是再次失去我们的童贞?
Couldn't we just lose our virginities again?
因为我觉得我的又长回来了
You know, because I think actually mine's growing back.
我要借一百块      什么?
I need $100.        What?
欢迎回家
Hi. Welcome home.
我要借一百块      为什么?
I need $100.        For what?
我要重新回到游戏之中
To get back in the game.
为什么? 你什么时候退出这个游戏的?
Why? When did you get out of the game?
我全赔了 赔光了      不会吧
I lost it all. Okay, I lost it.        Oh. no.
我已经跟他们达成协议了 你也要
I've come to terms with it, you have to too.
好吧
Okay.
看 额 摩妮卡 我很抱歉
Look, uh, Mon, I'm really sorry.
我们的一百块呢?
Where are we on the $100?
我没有一百块
I don't have it.
但是我需要!
But I need it!
不然我就不得不去做那份很烂的餐馆工作了
Otherwords I'm gonna have to take that horrible diner job.
你知道就是穿着戏服跳舞
You know, with the dancing and the costumes.
我不想戴阻燃剂做的假胸
I don't want to have to wear flame retardant boobs.
没人会想 亲爱的
Nobody does, honey.
你好
Hi.
面条!
Noodle!
老天 我的狗怎么了?
Oh, my God. What the hell happened to my dog?
那是个意外
It was an accident.
干了这个的人绝对不是故意伤害狗狗的
And the woman who did this would never hurt a dog on purpose.
她是个素食者
She's a vegetarian.
这是缝针么?
Are these stitches?
是的 8针 它身上总共缝了56针
Yeah, eight of them. That's 56 to him
另外如果下雨 不能让他向上看太久
You know also, if, if it's raining, you can't let him look up too long
因为那个圆锥形护颈很快就会满
because that cone will fill up really really fast.
多谢你把它剩余的部分带回来
Well, uh, thanks for bringing back what's left of him.
弗兰克在家吗?      你怎么会认识弗兰克?
Sure, is, is Frank home?        How do you know Frank?
额 认识很久了 他在吗?
Just from a long time ago. Is he here?
他在 弗兰克
Yeah. Frank.
干嘛?
Yeah.
What?
哦 好吧 额 我是指老弗兰克
Oh, okay, urn, I mean Frank Senior.
他出去买菜了
He went out for groceries.
那他会很快回来吗?
Will he be back soon?
他四年前就离开了
He left four years ago.
所以我们估计他很快就会回来了
We're expecting him back any minute.
好吧 我得走了
Alright, I, I'm gonna go.
关于狗的事 非常对不起 所有事
I'm sorry about the dog. Everything.
对不起
I'm sorry.
嗨 女士!
Hey, lady!
嗨 等等!
Hey, wait up!
你怎么认识我爸的?      额 其实我不认识
How do you know my dad?        Urn well, I don't really.
只是从基因角度看
Just genetically.
他也是我爸
He's kind of my dad too.
好沉重
Heavy.
是啊
Yeah.
他说起过我吗? 菲比?
So, urn, did he ever talk about me? Phoebe?
没有 但是他其实什么都不说的
No, but he didn't really talk about anything.
哦
Oh.
除了高跷
Except stilts.
高跷?      对 他喜欢踩高跷
Stilts?        Yeah. he loved stilts.
有一次我在楼上从我妈的包里面偷烟
One time, I was upstairs stealing cigarettes out of my mom's purse...
然后 忽然间我向外看...
and, uh, all of a sudden I look over...
我爸的脑袋正一蹦一跳地经过窗口
and there's Dad's head, bobbing past the window.
在他脸上有很开心的笑 他还向我挥手
He just had this big smile on his face and he was waving
因为他踩高跷的时候总是很高兴
because he was always happiest when he was on his stilts.
哇噢      是的
Wow.        Yeah.
我不知道怎么玩那东西
I don't know what to do with that.
我也不知道
Me neither
那么 你就是我的姐姐?      是的
So are you, like, my big sister?        Yeah.
那太好了 你可以给我买啤酒
This is huge. You can buy me beer
我不会买啤酒给你      哦
I'm not gonna.        Oh.
但是你知道什么事情很酷么?
But you know what's cool though?
如果你有叫皮特的朋友 我就可以说
Okay If you had a friend named Pete, I could say
"我认识皮特 他是我弟弟的朋友"
"I know Pete. He's friends with my brother."
我有个叫马克的朋友      那也可以
I got a friend named Mark.        That'll work too.
酷 真不错
Cool. All right.
或许 偶尔我可以给你电话
So maybe, you know, I could give you a call sometime.
我们可以聊聊什么的
We could talk or something.
没问题 那没问题      好的
Yeah, that'd be okay.        All right.
号码电话簿里有
Okay I'm in the book.
好的      好的
Okay yeah.        Okay, all right.
那么 高跷是吧?
So, urn, stilts, huh?
如果你愿意 我可以带你到后面
Yeah Hey you know, If you want, I can take you around back
看他的脑袋是在哪里撞到排水槽的
and show you where he hit his head on the rain gutter
好啊
Okay.
我们做到了 我们来到这里 站在我们的领地上
We did it. We're here. We are standing our ground.
弄杯咖啡要花多长的时间?
How long does coffee take?
你能不能快点! 快点!
Would you come on? Come on!
谢谢
Thank you.
我们做到了      我想我们已经证明了我们的能力
Ah, there we go.        I think we proved our point.
你烫到嘴了?      感觉不到舌头了
You burn your mouth?        Can not feel my tongue.
流氓! 超级流氓!
Bullies! Big bullies!
哦 看看谁在这儿 是小不点们
Oh. Look who's here. It's the weenies.
我们那天没说清楚么?
Did we not make ourselves clear the other day?
那就是我们来的原因
Yes That's why we're here.
对 我们站立在我们的领地上
Yes, we're standing our ground.
显然
Apparently.
我们来吧 哇哦哦
Let's do this already. Whoa, whoa.
你有什么 一个武器?
What'd you got there, a weapon?
这是只好表 我不想碎在你的肋骨上
A nice watch. I don't want to break it on your ribs.
好 我们开始吧
All right, let's do this.
我有问题 如果我不在乎我的手表
Question, If I don't care about my watch,
我能用来作为武器吗?
can I use it as a weapon?
什么意思?      这很尖锐 是金属的
What do you mean?        It's sharp, it's metal.
我想这能用来造成严重伤害
I think I can do, you know, some serious damage with it.
不行 你不能用你的表
No, you can't use your watch.
好吧
Okay.
或钥匙      好吧
Or your keys.        Okay
这样吧
Look, here's what we'll do.
我们把所有的钥匙和表放在帽子里 帽子放到那边
We'll put all keys and watches in the hat, over there.
好么?      好吧
All right?        All right.
好了 来吧
All right, come on, man. Let's do it!
在我忘了之前问一句 我们打脸吗?
Before I forget, are we hitting faces?
当然打脸了 为什么不打脸?
Of course we're hitting faces. Why wouldn't you hit faces?
周一我要上班 我有个很重要的演讲
Well because I have to work on Monday. I have a big presentation.
事实上 明天我要展示那个公寓
Actually, I gotta show this apartment tomorrow
不打脸算是个好主意
and, uh, this no faces thing might not be a bad idea.
好的 不打脖子以上
Okay, nothing from the neck up.
好的
All right.
或是腰以下
Or the waist down.
戴娜正在排卵期      真的么? 你们又在试了?
Dana's ovulating.        Oh, really? You guys trying again?
对啊
Yeah.
我直说了吧 我们就是指中间这部分?
Let me get this straight. So we're uh, strictly talking about the middle?
来呀!      喂! 喂! 哇哦!
Come on        Hey, hey, whoa!
你想被我揍么? 我就站在这儿呢!
You want a piece of this, huh? You want a piece of this, huh? I'm standing here!
喂! 喂! 那两个家伙拿我们的东西!
Huh! Hey, hey. Those guys are taking our stuff!
喂! 喂!
Hey, hey!
老天 太神奇了 刚才真是太不可思议了
God, that was amazing. That was incredible.
你们狠狠揍了那家伙一下!
You guys, you guys kicked butt!
我们? 你们才厉害
Us? What about you guys?
你从后面 "砰" 给了那家伙一下
You really, bing, gave it to old Mr. Clean back there.
那可是个大家伙      对 他是个大家伙 不是吗?
He was a big guy.        Yeah, he was, wasn't he?
我哪知道 我错过了所有的事情
I wouldn't know, having missed everything.
别这么说自己
Oh, don't do that to yourself.
我们每个人都有可能被那小女孩的跳绳绊倒的
Any one of us could have tripped over that little girl's jump rope.
嗯 听着 兄弟们 我们?
So listen, guys, are we, uh?
我们没问题了吧?
Are we okay here?
我们没问题      好的
We're okay.        Ha, ha, all right.
我能要回我的帽子么?
Okay, so can I have my hat back?
不行
No.
天呐 你们看她
Oh, my God. Look at her.
你好 摩妮卡!
Hi Monica!
乔伊     怎么样?
Joey        How's it going?
胸部好漂亮
Hey, nice boobs.
你们看看这个
Guys, guys. Check this out.
太棒了
Excellent.